You've cleared the game. What did you think?
So, this is the second Spice & Wolf DS game...
Ah~ Lawrence finally made an appearance.
I missed him last time, hah-hah.
So, how was it to become Lawrence?
Spending time with the female characters...
getting into all kinds of trouble,
and having fun while clearing events.
So, did you enjoy Holo's route?
Ah, you preferred Eve's?
Huh? You liked Norah's?
Haaah, Luka? Heh-heh, how naughty~ Heh.
Well, there's all kinds of characters,
so I'm sure there must be one you like.
Huh...? No way!
Lawrence is your favorite?!
Huh, I see. I wasn't expecting that.
Are beards also popular with men?
Oh, you're a woman? Whoops.
I hope that this game will be supported
by people of all ages and sexes.
Now you've seen this, you can start again.
I hope you can reaffirm your favorites.
I'll work hard to try and become one.
Alright! Thank you, everyone.
Jun Fukuyama playing Lawrence.